let quiz=[
    {
        question:	
        "Suppose that you would like to create an instance of a new Map that has an iteration order that is the same as the iteration order of an existing instance of a Map. Which concrete implementation of the Map interface should be used for the new instance?",
        option:[
            "1.TreeMap",
            "2.HashMap",
            "3.LinkedHashMap",
            "4.The answer depends on the implementation of the existing instance.",
        ],
        answer:3,
    },
    {
        question:" Which class does not override the equals() and hashCode() methods, inheriting them directly from class Object?",
        option:[
            "1.java.lang.String",
            "2.java.lang.Double",
            "3.	java.lang.StringBuffer",
            "4.	java.lang.Character",
            
        ],
        answer:3,
    },
    {
        question:"In JavaScript the x===y statement implies that:",
        option:[
            "1.Both x and y are equal in value, type and reference address as well.",
            "2.Both are x and y are equal in value only.",
            "3.Both are equal in the value and data type.",
           "4.Both are not same at all.",   
        ],
        answer:3,
    },
    {
        question:"Which collection class allows you to grow or shrink its size and provides indexed access to its elements, but whose methods are not synchronized?",
        option:[
            "1.java.util.HashSet",
            "2.java.util.LinkedHashSet ",
            "3.java.util.List",
            "4.java.util.ArrayList",   
        ],
        answer:4,

    },
    {
        question:"You need to store elements in a collection that guarantees that no duplicates are stored and all elements can be accessed in natural order. Which interface provides that capability?",
        option:[
            "1.java.util.Map",
            "2.java.util.Set",
            "3.	java.util.List",
            "4. java.util.Collection",   
        ],
        answer:2,
    },
    {
        question:"Which collection class allows you to grow or shrink its size and provides indexed access to its elements, but whose methods are not synchronized?",
        option:[
            "1.java.util.HashSet",
            "2.java.util.LinkedHashSet",
            "3.java.util.List",
            "4.java.util.ArrayList",   
        ],
        answer:4,
    },

{
        question:	
        "You need to store elements in a collection that guarantees that no duplicates are stored and all elements can be accessed in natural order. Which interface provides that capability?",
        option:[
            "1.java.util.Map",
            "2.java.util.Set",
            "3.java.util.List",
            "4.	java.util.Collection",   
        ],
        answer:2,
    },

    {
        question:	
        	
        "Which is valid declaration of a float?",
        option:[
            "1.float f = 1F;",
            "2.float f = 1.0;",
            "3.float f = 1 ; ",
            "4.	float f = 1.0d;",   
        ],
        answer:1,
    },

    {
        question:	
        "What is the numerical range of char?",
        option:[
            "1. 0 to 32767",
            "2. 0 to 65535",
            "3. -256 to 255",
            "4. -32768 to 32767",
        ],
        answer:2,
    },

    {
        question:	
    	
        "Which is true about an anonymous inner class?",
        option:[
            "1. It can extend exactly one class and implement exactly one interface.",
            "2. It can extend exactly one class and can implement multiple interfaces.",
            "3. It can extend exactly one class or implement exactly one interface.",
            "4. It can implement multiple interfaces regardless of whether it also extends a class.",
        ],
        answer:3,
    },
]